[
  {
    "qId": 1,
    "question": "Aesthetics are not important if you have good usability ?",
    "options": ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    "gyan": "There are set of practitioners who completely dismiss the importance of aesthetics, often citing unattractive but popular websites such as Craigslist.",
    "answer": "FALSE"
  },

  {
    "qId": 2,
    "question": "Search is used by user when they are unable to find a good navigational link ?",
    "options": ["TRUE","FALSE"],
    "gyan": "On a website, people usually scan for trigger words first and only use the search function when they’re unable to find a good enough navigational link.",
    "answer": "TRUE"
  },

  {
    "qId": 3,
    "question": "All pages should be accessible in 3 clicks ?",
    "options": ["TRUE","FALSE"],
    "gyan": "The number of necessary clicks affects neither user satisfaction, nor success rate. Fewer clicks don’t make users happier and aren’t necessarily perceived as faster.",
    "answer": "FALSE"
  },

  {
    "qId": 4,
    "question": "Customer is always right ?",
    "options": ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    "gyan": "Henry Ford once stated, \"If I asked people what they wanted, they would have said faster horses.\"",
    "answer": "FALSE"
  },

  {
    "qId": 5,
    "question": "5 Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 6,
    "question": "6 Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  },

  {
    "qId": 7,
    "question": "7 Who invented Design ?",
    "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 8,
    "question": "8 Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 9,
    "question": "9 Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  },

  {
    "qId": 10,
    "question": "10 Who invented Design ?",
    "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 11,
    "question": " 11 Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Smith"
  },
  {
    "qId": 12,
    "question": "12 Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": [
      "Somya",
      "Ruchi"
    ],
    "gyan": "Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah",
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  }
]
